O Land of the Free by the Carib Sea
Our manhood we pledge to thy liberty
No tyrants here linger, despots must flee
This tranquil haven of democracy
The blood of our sires which hallows the sod
Brought freedom from slavery, oppression's rod
By the might of truth, and the grace of God
No longer shall we be hewers of wood
Arise! ye sons of the Baymen's clan
Put on your armour, clear the land
Drive back the tyrants, let despots flee
Land of the Free by the Carib Sea
Nature has blessed thee with wealth untold
O'er mountains and valleys where prairies roll
Our fathers, the Baymen, valiant and bold
Drove back the invader; this heritage hold
From proud Rio Hondo to old Sarstoon
Through coral isle, over blue lagoon
Keep watch with the angels, the stars and moon
For freedom comes tomorrow's noon
Arise! ye sons of the Baymen's clan
Put on your armour, clear the land
Drive back the tyrants, let despots flee
Land of the Free by the Carib Sea